A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Frederick Seitz FA1069
Rockefeller Archive Center
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Pennsylvania - Stennler, 1979-1984 (Box 39, Folder 12-14)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Pennsylvania - Morgan, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Pennsylvania - Owen, 1979-1980 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Pittsburgh - Sandra Levy, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Rochester Medical Center - Ader, 1984-1988 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Southern California - Heidelberger, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of South Florida - Spielberger and Williams, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Vermont - Krawisz, 1986-1988 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Utah - Matsen, 1981-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - University of Washington - Ross, 1976-1987 (Box 40, Folder 3-10)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - W. Alton Jones Science Center, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Washinton University - Lacy, 1971-1979 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Webb-Waring Lung Institute, Denver, CO, 1979-1986 (Box 40, Folder 13-14)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Wistar Institute, 1978-1985 (Box 40, Folder 15-16)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Wistar Institute, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Yale University - Powell and Oslfeld, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- R. J. Reynolds - Biomedical Research Program - Grant Files - Yale University School of Medicine - Palade-Farquhar, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1975 - A-Z (Box 41, Folder 6-29)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1976 - A-Z (Box 42, Folder 1-24)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1977 - A-R (Box 43, Folder 1-21)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1977 - S-Z (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1978 - A-Z (Box 44, Folder 6-29)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1979 - A-Z (Box 45, Folder 1-22)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1980 - A-Z (Box 45, Folder 23-44)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1981 - A-Z (Box 45, Folder 45-66)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1982 - A-Z (Box 46, Folder 1-24)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1983 - A-Z (Box 46, Folder 25-48)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1984 - A-C (Box 46, Folder 49-51)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1984 - D-Z (Box 47, Folder 1-21)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1985 - A-Z (Box 47, Folder 22-29)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1986 - A-Z (Box 47, Folder 30-33)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1987 - A-Z (Box 48, Folder 1-20)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1988 - A-Z (Box 48, Folder 21-27)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1989 - A-Z (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1990 - A-Z (Box 49, Folder 6-10)
- Alphabetical Correspondence - 1991 - A-Z (Box 49, Folder 11-16)
- ABM Program, 1969-1971 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- ABM Program - Senate Hearing, 1969 April 22-23 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- American Museum of Natural History, 1969-1979 (Box 50, Folder 3-10)
- John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1969-1974 (Box 50, Folder 11-13)
- John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Institute of International Education (IIE) - Board Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
- Ampex Corporation, 1965-1977 (Box 51, Folder 4-6)
  Restricted - Confidential material
- Seitz Speeches - Drafts, 1963-1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Turnbull, 1958-1967 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Jacoby Letters, 1962-1963 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Ehrenreich, 1966-1968 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Publishers, 1953-1959 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Review of Solid State Physics, 1956-1960 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - Publishers, 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Publishers, 1966-1969 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Information on Prospective Manuscripts, Academic Press, 1957-1966 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Academic Press - A, 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Academic Press - B-Bo, 1955-1965 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Academic Press - Br, 1957-1964 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Academic Press - C, 1955-1961 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Academic Press - D, 1955-1962 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Academic Press - E-F, 1955-1963 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Academic Press - G, 1959-1968 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Academic Press - H, 1954-1969 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Academic Press - I-Ke, 1955-1966 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Academic Press - Ki, 1956-1967 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Academic Press - L, 1956-1966 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Academic Press - M, 1955-1968 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Academic Press - N-O, 1956-1966 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Academic Press - P-Sen, 1955-1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Academic Press - Sh, 1955-1963 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Academic Press - T-Wa, 1955-1961 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Academic Press - We-Z, 1955-1966 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Alan Liss, 1954-1965 (Box 53, Folder 8-9)
- David Turnbull, 1953-1957 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC), 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 1-13)
  Board of Directors and Committee meeting files as well as program and policy, budget and finance materials pertaining to MSKCC, Memorial Hospital and Sloan-Kettering Institute.
- Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC), 1974-1979 (Box 55, Folder 1-13)
- Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC), 1970-1973 (Box 56, Folder 1-5)
- American Institute of Physics (AIP), 1969-1973 (Box 56, Folder 6-14)
- American Institute of Physics (AIP), 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
- American Institute of Physics (AIP) - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Sciences (NAS) - Five-Year Outlook, 1980-1982 (Box 57, Folder 4-12)
- National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1972-1978 (Box 58, Folder 1-16)
- National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder 1-4)
- Scientists and Engineers for Secure Energy, Inc., 1977-1981 (Box 59, Folder 5-10)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation - Jane Goodall Lecture, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box 59, Folder 15-18)
- L. S. B. Leakey Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 1-3)
- Institute of International Education (IIE), 1974-1986 (Box 60, Folder 4-13)
- Institute of International Education (IIE), 1972-1977 (Box 61, Folder 1-10)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Background Information, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Committee Chairman, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Committee Members, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Financial (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - FDA-Fdil (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Invitations (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Lushbough, Channing, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Seitz, Frederick, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Meetings, 1974 February 6 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Meetings, 1973 June 5-6 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Meetings, 1973 May 4 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Minutes, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply -Nutrition Foundation, 1962-1974 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Special Commission on Internal Pollution, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Citizens Commission of Science, Law and the Food Supply - Wellford, Harrison, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Publications Pending, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Seitz List of Papers and Articles, 1962-1974 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- Seitz List of Publications, 1932-1969 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Seitz, 1974 MIM and Johns Hopkins (Box 62, Folder 16)
- Seitz List of Reprints, 1964-1968 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- Lehigh University, 1970-1974 (Box 62, Folder 18-23)
- Lehigh University, 1975-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1-8)
- Lehigh University - Solid State Science, 1973-1974 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Lehigh University, 1979-1982 (Box 63, Folder 10-15)
- Miscellaneous Information, 1955-1964 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Seitz - Reprints (Box 64, Folder 2-4)
- Seitz - Positions Offerred, 1954-1963 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Seitz - Contracts at Illinois, 1953-1964 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Seitz - Patent Applications, 1953-1958 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Seitz - Insurance and Annuity, 1949-1964 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Seitz - Personal Letters - 1, 1949-1955 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Seitz - Personal Letters - 2, 1956-1961 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Seitz - Personal Letters - 3, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Seitz - Personal Letters - 4, 1962-1963 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Seitz - Personal Letters - Current, 1964-1966 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- National Research Council (NRC) - Reports, 1969-1974 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- National Research Council (NRC) - General, 1969-1974 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- National Research Council (NRC) - Minutes and Notes, 1971-1977 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- National Research Council (NRC) - Correspondence, 1969-1975 (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
- National Research Council (NRC), 1975-1979 (Box 65, Folder 6-9)
- Princeton - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Princeton - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Princeton - Minutes - Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Princeton - Minutes - Board of Trustees, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Princeton - Alumni Annual Giving, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 14)
- Princeton - General Information, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Princeton - Invitations, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- Princeton - Library Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Princeton - Physics Advisory Panel, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Princeton - Presidential Search Committee, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- Princeton - Curriculum Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Princeton - Graduate Alumni, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Princeton - Honorary Degree Committee, 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- Princeton - Finance Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- Princeton - Committee on Plans and Resources, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Princeton - President's Report, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rican Nuclear Center (PRNC) - Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rican Nuclear Center (PRNC) - Budgets, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rican Nuclear Center (PRNC) - General, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rican Nuclear Center (PRNC), 1969-1973 (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
- Research Corporation, 1969-1976 (Box 66, Folder 8-14)
- Research Corporation - Minutes, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 15)
- Research Corporation - Minutes, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 16)
- Adler Prize, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- GAO lecture by Seitz, 1974 November 4 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Rome Lecture, 1975-1977 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- North Carolina State Sponsored Residential High School - Informal Advisory Group to Guide Planning Committee, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- Claremont File, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Bicentennial Science Planning Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Rockefeller University President's Report 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Schmidt, Benno C., 1972-1976 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Scientific American, 1973-1974 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Schmidt, Rose, 1971-1974 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Sachs, Mendel, 1969-1972 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Schmidt, Benno - Zinder, Norton (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Celebration for Professor Herman Mark, 1975 May 3 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Awards and Prize Committee, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Manuscripts-pending Lucknow University - India, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- NASA - Sci. Astronaut Program, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Said, H. M., 1971-1973 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- Samis, Sidney M. (and son Peter S. Samis), 1974 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Salk Institute, San Diego, CA, 1970-1971 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- NMR Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1969-1976 (Box 67, Folder 17-29)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 68, Folder 1-5)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Minutes, 1972-1974 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Finance Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 68, Folder 7-8)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Nominating Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 9-10)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Committee on Audit, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Capital Management, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Rockefeller Foundation - Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1969-1975 (Box 68, Folder 14-16)
- Texas Instruments, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 69, Folder 1-5)
- Texas Instruments - Bryan Smith, 1978-1981 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Texas Instruments - William J. Roche, 1979-1982 (Box 69, Folder 7-8)
- Texas Instruments - Fred Bucy, 1978-1983 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Texas Instruments - Audit Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Texas Instruments, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 11-15)
- Texas Instruments - Patrick Haggerty, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Texas Instruments - Mark Shepherd, 1979-1983 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- Volunteers in Technical Assistance (VITA) - General, 1969-1972 (Box 70, Folder 1-5)
- Volunteers in Technical Assistance (VITA) - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 70, Folder 6-7)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA), 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 8-11)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA) - LSI Monthly Newsletter, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA) - Minutes, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 13-15)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA) - Minutes and Reports, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA) - Minutes and Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 71, Folder 2-8)
- Universities Space Research Association (USRA) - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 9-10)
- Universities Research Association, 1970-1977 (Box 71, Folder 11-14)
- University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR), 1975-1980 (Box 72, Folder 1-12)
- Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation (WWNFF), 1971-1979 (Box 73, Folder 1-8)
- Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation International Center (Smithsonian), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute, 1973-1976 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - On the Issue of Nuclear Power, University of Guelph, 1989 October (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Crucial Steps in the Evolution of Science org. Version Pwpa, London, 1989 August (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Nuclear Science - Promises and Perceptions, George Washington University, 1989 January 17 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - A Safari Through Physics in South Africa, 1989 July (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - UNESCO Visit, 1988 February 14 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - A Physicists View of Living Systems Icus, Los Angeles, CA, Nov-88 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Solid State Physics and Italian-American Interaction Pavia, Italy, 1987 September 21-24 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - ICUS - International Congress of Professors World Peace Academy, London, 1989 August 25-29 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Seitz on Francis Wheeler Loomes, 1987 June 10 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Comments on Strategic Defensive Systems used Against an Attack in Boost Phase, 1987 August (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Matching Reality to Need "Technology in Society", Final Draft, 1987 July 1 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - A Personalized History of the Evolution of Materials Sciences, Materials and Future Society Symposium, Tokyo, 1986 November 10-12 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - NATO Conference - Introductory Statement and Closing Remarks, 1986 February 6-8 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commemoration of the 25th Anniversary of Laboratory for Research on Structure of Matter, Special Convocation, University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia, 1985 December 16 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Clarence Zener 80th Birthday Celebration, Carnegie Mellon, Pittsburgh, 1985 November 23 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Memorial Symposium in Honor of Heinz Pick., Stuttgart, 1985 November 5 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Whitney Symposium on Science and Technology VI Electronic Materials and Structures, 1985 June 11 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commemorative Lecture Tenth Anniversary Foundation, 1985 April (Box 74, Folder 18)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commentary on Ota Report on Ballistic Missle Defense Technology, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Book Review "Haphazard Reality" by Casimer for "Foundations of Physics", 1985 January (Box 74, Folder 20)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commemorative Lecture on the Occasion of the Tenth Anniversary of Radiation Effects Research Foundation, Hiroshima City, Japan, 1985 April 19 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commemorative Lecture on the Occasion of the Tenth Anniversary of Radiation Effects Research Foundation, Hiroshima City, Japan, 1985 April 19 (Box 74, Folder 22)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Patrick E. Haggerty Building Dedication at University of Dallas, 1985 March 30 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Allen V. Astin Memorial Symposium speech "Controversies Affecting Science Today", National Bureau of Standards, 1985 January 28 (Box 74, Folder 24)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Whitney Symposium on Science and Technology, General Electric, Schenectady, NY, 1985 June 11 (Box 74, Folder 25)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Commencement Speech, University of Rochester, 1984 May 6 (Box 74, Folder 26)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Speech for Walter Elsasser's 80th Birthday, Johns Hopkins, Baltimore, 1984 May 4 (Box 74, Folder 27)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Visiting Committee, University of Rochester, 1984 May 6-8 (Box 74, Folder 28)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Survival Without Science, University of Arkansas, 1984 March 6 (Box 74, Folder 29)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - IEEE Annual Fellows Awards Dinner - Speech - Trends in the World of Science and Technology, 1984 February 17 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Guggenheim Foundation Dinner - Speech, 1984 February 16 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Society at Risk Speech, University of Missouri, Kansas City, 1983 November 1 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Shih-Liang Chien Memorial Talk, 1983 October 23 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - USIA Report of Visits to Western Europe. Embassies and Labs re: Use of Chemical Weapons in Afghanistan and Southeast Asia, 1983 July 11-19 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Vannevar Bush Award Speech, 1983 May 18 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - RJR Research Grants Program Update, 1983 May 2 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Speech - On the Question of the Nuclear Shield - Erice, Sicily, 1982 August (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - American Chemical Society Symposium Speech - The Role of Science in Development, Las Vegas, 1982 March 30 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - University of Illinois Talk, Koehler and Maurer, 1981 October 8 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Memorial Tribute - Philip Handler, National Academy of Sciences, 1982 February 8 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Presentation to Conference on the Challenge of the 80's Science and Technology in the University, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1981 November 9-12 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Dr. Wolman's Conference on Terrorism, Introductory Statement by Seitz, 1981 October 2 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Report on R. J. Reynolds Research Grants Program, Draft, 1981 August 6 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Cancer and the Molecular Biologist, Draft, 1981 August 6 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Book Review - Sci. Quest Seeds of Discovery by W. I. B. Beveridge, 1981 June 26 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Speech - Committee of Concerned Scientists, Inc. Convocation Meeting, New York Academy of Sciences, 1981 February 8 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Book Review - Bulletin of Atomic Scien., America's Technology Slip, Simon Ramo, 1981 February 10 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Reprints of Articles by Seitz in Bulletin of Atomic Scientist May 1980 - Reflections on UNCSTD, 1980 May (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Book Review - Pergamon Press Science, Technology and Global Problems - Views from the Developing World, 1980 March (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Wheeler Loomes Dedication, Remarks by Seitz, University of Illinois, 1980 February 14 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - UNESTED Report, 1979 November 16 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Ogden Presentation, 1979 November 7 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Draft, Center for History of Physics, American Institute of Physics, 1979 December (Box 75, Folder 24)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - NAE - Presentation, 1979 November 1 (Box 75, Folder 25)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - R. J. Reynolds - Presentation, Bermuda, 1979 November 3-6 (Box 75, Folder 26)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - R. J. Reynolds - Operating Committee - Presentation, 1979 August 8 (Box 75, Folder 27)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - R. J. Reynolds - Talk, 1979 May 29 (Box 75, Folder 28)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - A Physicists View of Living Systems (Box 75, Folder 29)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - University of Port Elizabeth - Commencement Address, 1979 March (Box 75, Folder 30)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - London Meeting, Royal Society, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 31)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Status of Higher Education in the Atlantic Community (Box 75, Folder 32)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - The American University, SUNY-Albany, NY, 1977 October 25 (Box 75, Folder 33)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Perspectives in Solid State Science (Box 75, Folder 34)
- Speeches, Lectures, Articles - Contributions of Education and Research Program to Manpower and Advances in the Space Sciences (Box 75, Folder 35)